dhtmlx.com 2019-04-15

# Privacy Policy - DHTMLX

**Last updated: April 18, 2018.**

At Dinamenta UAB, we take care of your privacy and make every effort to guarantee the security of your personal data and provide you with a safe stay on our Site (https://dhtmlx.com/). We developed this in-depth privacy statement to keep you informed about the data we collect, how the data is used and general information on using this Site. If some items of this privacy policy seem unsuitable for you, we recommend you not to use our software products, services and information of this Site. 

###### Information We Collect

When you send a request to evaluate the product(s), request information about our products and services using the contact forms, you may provide us with your personal data such as your name, your email address, your company name. We do not collect any additional personal data unless you provide it voluntarily using the comments section of the contact forms. 

We may also collect your personal data when you take part in our survey, contests or register for the participation in special offers. 

When you use our Site, we may collect non personal (anonymous) data such as duration of your visit, the pages you visit on our Site, browser type, device type, country, city, referral site you are coming from (if any), etc. This is not a full and comprehensive list of anonymous data we collect, and it's based on the features and abilities of the third party analytics software we use (see next chapter). In this case we exclusively collect such information that does not allow us to identify you; this type of information is used only for statistical work. The better we understand your needs, the faster you will find the required information on our Site. 

###### Third Party Analytics Software

This Site uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google") and Yandex Metrica, a web analytics service provided by Yandex, Ltd. ("Yandex"). These services help us to improve your experience of visiting our Site. They use cookies that are stored on your computer/device and contain information about your visit: duration, visited pages, country, browser type, device type, etc. To learn more about Google Analytics, including how to opt out of it, visit <https://www.google.com/analytics/> and <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>. 

Yandex Metrica helps us to get statistical data about visitors' behaviour on our Site. Yandex Metrica may record mouse clicks, mouse movements, scrolling activity, etc. By analysing the received statistical data, we are able to improve the navigation and design of the site to provide our users with better experience and ability to find and use the information of our Site faster and more efficiently. To learn more about Yandex Metrica, visit <https://metrica.yandex.com/about>. 

###### Facebook Audiences and Google Adwords Audiences

We use advertising functionality of Facebook (pixels) that is added to our Site's pages and allows us to send data about visitors' actions performed on our Site. By means of pixels, Facebook creates custom audiences of people who visit specific pages or set of pages and/or make a conversion. We do not transfer or disclose any personally identifiable information to Facebook. 

By means of Google Analytics, we may create custom audiences of people who visit a particular page or set of pages or/and make any conversion on our Site. We use Display Advertising Remarketing by Google Adwords to show specific and relevant ads to the created audiences. We do not transfer or disclose any personally identifiable information to Google. You may adjust the settings of the ads you want or do not want to see here: <https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads/authenticated>. 

###### Orders and Information Connected to Orders

We use third party e-commerce provider for processing your orders and payments. All the payment documents such as receipts, invoices, payment confirmation are sent to you by this provider. When submitting your order, you may provide some personal information such as name, email address, postal address, telephone number, company name. When you pay by credit/debit card for your order, you provide the credentials of your credit/debit card. 

After your payment is processed, our provider sends us a part of your personal data: name, email address, company name, telephone number and Order ID assigned to your purchase (at the same time, this Order ID is your License ID as well). We receive this information to be able to send you the relevant license information, the download link to the software product and your credentials to login to the Clients Area and Support Center. We do not receive and/or collect your payment data (the credentials of your credit card or some other payment information). 

According to the information from our provider, it has confirmed its status of accredited Level 1 Service Provider, following a comprehensive auditing process performed by GRSee Consulting, an independent Quality Security Assessor (QSA). PCI-DSS is the worldwide information security standard set by the Payment Card Industry Security Standards Council, to ensure full security of sensitive data and protection against risks of fraud. 

###### Cookies

Our Site uses cookies to track preferences of the visitors of the Site and subsequent optimization of its design. Cookies are small text files that are stored on visitor's computer/device. They facilitate the navigation and make the whole visit of the Site more comfortable. Cookies may also be used to determine whether your computer/device visited this Site before. Cookies may contain your personal data only in case you gave the appropriate permission for this (for example, login credentials for your cabinet). You can visit our Site with cookies disabled as well. The majority of web browsers have the cookies enabled by default, but you can check your settings and disable them by yourself. Also you can delete all cookies that are stored on your computer/device at any time. We also inform you that disabling cookies may prevent you from using some of the services of our Site. 

###### How We Use Information

We may use the personal data collected from you and the product you use or evaluate with the following purposes: 

  * To provide you with the links to the relevant version of the product(s) and your login details to Clients Area and Support Center. 
  * To send you the supporting and learning materials corresponding to the product(s) you use or evaluate. 
  * During the evaluation period, we may send you the information about the product's features, documentation, samples, support services, licenses and other corresponding information. 
  * To inform you about new releases of the product(s) and services. 
  * To inform you about any changes to the product(s) and services usage terms and conditions. 
  * To inform you about new products. 
  * To provide you with the technical and non-technical support. 
  * To get your feedback on product(s) and services you use or evaluate to improve the quality and adjust the roadmap. 
  * To get your feedback on the documentation and the quality of the work of technical support team. 
  * To inform you about special offers that are relevant to the product(s) you use or evaluate. 
  * To get a testimonial or a case study that will be published on our website and company's social media accounts. The contents of the published material will be discussed with you prior to the publication. 
  * To reply to your feedback that you may leave after the use or evaluation of the product(s). 
  * To inform you about the expiration of your support/updates subscription (both by phone and email). 

We store your personal data only for the period of time required to provide you with the relevant information and check whether you are entitled to get paid technical support. That means since you give us your consent for processing your personal data, we will store it according to your consent and/or till you withdraw your consent. 

###### Marketing Communication

When you get our product for evaluation or purchase a license from us, you may occasionally receive promotional emails. We are considering your interests in the specific products and in most cases these emails contain relevant information about special offers, contests, new products and services, updated products and services that you show interest in. We send this information by direct emails ourselves, or via third party email service providers. 

At any time, you may stop receiving marketing and promotional information by clicking "Unsubscribe" at the bottom of each email or sending us a direct request to unsubscribe you from further promotional emails. 

We inform you that in case you unsubscribe from receiving our promotional emails that may include information about product updates, you may miss news about these updates. Nevertheless, you will still be able to visit our blog yourself or login to the Clients Area to get the relevant information. If you purchase a license for our product(s) and unsubscribe from promotional emails, you will still get notifications about your support/updates period expiration as we do not consider this type of emails promotional but informational one. 

###### Community Forum

You may register at our free community Forum to get free technical/non-technical help from other forum users and/or our moderators. When you create a new topic on the Forum or send any message to other topics, you are responsible for any personal information you provide in your posts. Any visitor or member of the Forum may have an access to your public posts and send you personal messages. 

###### Retention and Deletion of Your Data

We store personal information of our evaluation users and customers to have the possibility to send new updates and news about the products they obtained. In addition, we need this personal data to have reasons to provide official paid technical support that is available only in case if a client has an active support subscription. Nevertheless, you have the right to request the deletion of your personal information and we confirm that the data will be deleted within 30 days. To make such a request, please contact us at [info](). 

###### Links to Other Websites

Our Site may contain links to other sites. Please note that we are not responsible for your security on other sites so remember to study their privacy policy and other terms. 

###### Legal Disclaimer

Dinamenta UAB reserves the right to disclose your personal data in the following cases: 

  * In accordance with requirements of the legislation, for example, in connection with demands from governmental authorities, legal and contractual disputes. 
  * In case we believe that the disclosure of the personal data is necessary to protect our rights and safety. For example, to study the possible violation of our terms of use; to identify, prevent or reveal fraud or any other problems connected with security. 

###### Security

The data you entered on this Site is automatically encrypted using SSL (Sockets Layer Protocol). SSL is the industry standard for transferring sensitive data over the internet. 

In order to protect your data from fraud, leakage and damage, Dinamenta UAB takes a number of technical and organizational security measures. As the technological progress rises, we improve these measures. 

###### Changes in this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time. The date of the latest changes is stated at the top of this Privacy Policy page. In case of important changes we may inform you by email. Nevertheless, we encourage you to visit this Privacy Policy page from time to time especially when you do not visit our Site for a long time. 

###### How to Contact Us

If you have any questions related to this Privacy Policy or security of this Site, please write us at [info]().
